Aleksandar Grubić

21000 Novi Sad | +381606652522 | hello@aleksandargrubic.com

https://aleksandargrubic.com/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aleksandar-grubic

I am Cloud Enthusiast and an experienced Field Service Engineer. My current job duties usually include inspecting and installing equipment and new technologies, directing crews or workers on site, conducting research, and reporting on project status. These years I have been focusing also on DevOps technologies and I believe that this is the right moment and chance to face the new challenges that this role is offering.

Cloud Experience

CURRENTLY LEARNING:

- Vagrant Automatic installation of virtual machine, provisioning and server configuration, website setup, WordPress setup;
- AWS(Amazon Web Service) Installing and configuring EC2 machines, creating Elastic Block Storage, creating EBS snapshots, Elastic Load Balancer, Cloudwatch, Auto Scaling Group.
- CI/CD tools(Jenkins) and Python

Professional Experience

Euromedicina

January 2017 - Present

Field Service Engineer

- Working in a dynamic environment. Troubleshooting, repairing and maintaining Hematology, Biochemistry, and Immunochemistry analyzers, lot of traveling, Customer training & Technical Support;
- Repairing computers and following equipment for analyzers;
- Ordering parts, communicating with producers and generating reports.

Aces

January 2016 – June 2016

Frontend Developer

- Working on a software tool for tennis coaches and players called ACES
- HTML; CSS; SASS; JavaScript; Bootstrap.

Elins Plus

May 2014 – December 2015

Telecommunication Field Service Engineer

- Coaxial and optical cable installation, amplifier calibration
- Installing of telecommunications equipment.

Xeon doo

December 2013 – May 2014

Computer Service/ Alarm and video surveillance

- Repair, troubleshoot, and maintain computers, and equipment. Data backup and restoring lost data & passwords of user accounts;
- Installing and adjusting alarm and video surveillance at customer sites

Education

Technical school, Kikinda Computer electrician

Interests

• 3D modeling/remodeling/upgrading and printing plastic parts for the projects and repairing stuff